<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Quang Hugo</title><link>https://quanghugo.pages.dev/categories/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Quang Hugo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quanghugo.pages.dev/categories/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://quanghugo.pages.dev/p/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quanghugo.pages.dev/p/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;new blog&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; about technical exploration! Here, I will share my learning journey about the tech world around us. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned developer or just starting out, I hope this space becomes a valuable resource for learning, inspiration, and technical discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="what-ill-do-at-wang-tech"&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;ll do at Wang-tech
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="learning-process"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learning process&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll document my journey of mastering new technologies, frameworks, and programming languages. This includes tutorials, step-by-step guides, common pitfalls I encounter, and how I overcome challenges. Expect detailed explanations, code examples, and practical tips that you can apply to your own projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="new-technology"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Technology&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll explore cutting-edge technologies, tools, and trends in the software development world. From AI and machine learning to cloud computing, microservices architecture, and modern web frameworks - I&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into what makes these technologies exciting and how they can be leveraged in real-world applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="my-tech-life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My tech-life&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond just technical content, I&amp;rsquo;ll share insights from my daily life as a developer. This includes project experiences, lessons learned from building applications, code reviews, debugging adventures, and reflections on best practices. You&amp;rsquo;ll get a glimpse into the real-world challenges and triumphs of software development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="whats-next"&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I embark on this blogging journey, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my upcoming adventures:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project walkthroughs&lt;/strong&gt;: Real-world applications from concept to deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech stack comparisons&lt;/strong&gt;: When to use what technology and why&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem-solving sessions&lt;/strong&gt;: Breaking down complex technical challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry insights&lt;/strong&gt;: Trends, best practices, and lessons from the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community engagement&lt;/strong&gt;: Discussions, Q&amp;amp;As, and collaborative learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to connecting with fellow developers and tech enthusiasts. Your feedback and suggestions will help shape the direction of this blog. Together, we can build a community that thrives on knowledge sharing and continuous improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for joining me on this journey. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the fascinating world of technology together!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>